now let's do a quiz on the benefits of
Branch prediction let's say we have the
classical five-stage pipeline the fetch
decode ALU memory and right the branch
is fully resolved in the ALU the third
stage fully resolved means that we
finally know the correct PC from which
we should fetch the next instruction in
this processor we fetch nothing until we
are sure what to fetch and we execute
many many iterations of this Loop we add
my - 1 to R1 we add R2 to itself and
then we Branch if R1 is not equal zero
back to the loop the question for you
what is the speed up over this achieved
if we had perfect predictor meaning for
after every instruction is fetched we
knew which one should be fetched next